Brooke Mortensen

Front End Web Developer

801.556.6803



brookemorte@gmail.com



linkedin.com/in/brookemortensen (in)



github.com/brookemo



profile

Front End Web Developer able to build a sophisticated website that not only looks great but works great too. Loves learning new technologies, and quick to pick up on them. Understands the importance of User Experience. Loves simple and clean work.

skills

Node.js, Express, JavaScript, jQuery, React.js, Handlebars JS, GIT, Github, MySQL, Firebase, HTML, CSS, Bootstrap, Materialize, Media Queries, APIs, JSON, REST, AJAX, and the command line.

education

FULL STACK BOOTCAMP

University of Utah
January 2018 - July 2018
An intensive 24-week long
bootcamp dedicated to building
web applications from start to
finish.

past experience

CUSTOMER SERVICE

Wordpress Editor @
SIngle Dad Laughing
January 2018 - March 2018
Spa Concierge @
The Grand America Hotel
October 2015 - January 2018

applications built

SK8

Front End Developer

A web application that allows users to create a profile and share skating tricks with other skaters in their area.

I used Javascript, JSON, jQuery, AJAX calls, HTML, CSS, Materialize, the Geolocation API and the Google Maps APIs.

https://stark-savannah-69359.herokuapp.com/

AVENGERS ASSEMBLER

Front End Developer

A web application that connects users to information regarding their favorite Avengers Characters.

I worked on a team, and was responsible for the front end development of the character pages., and all mobile responsiveness. Using HTML, CSS, Bootstrap, Javascript, and the IMBD/OMBD API.

https://clickomat.github.io/goonies/

CRYSTAL COLLECTOR GAME

Full Stack Developer

A web application game that allows users to click on crystals to try to add up to a randomized number.

I used HTML, CSS, Javascript, and jQuery. brookemo.github.io/CrystalsCollectorGame/